HDFC Bank, RIL, TCS, Lemontree, ICICI
Lobbard are among stocks in focus next week. Yes, why
results next week? Reliance
Industries, TCS, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank,
Infosys, HCL Technologies, Jio Finance
Services, Wipro, Yes Bank and others will
post their quarterly results in the
coming week. Data compiled from BSE suggests
corporate actions. Tata Consultancy
Services, TCS, Kotak Mahindra Bank, Authum
Investment and Infrastructure, Amer RT
& Infra India, and Best Agro Life are among stocks which would turn
X dates
for corporate action next week. BSE
data showed ICICI Lumb General Insurance Company
informed the
stock exchanges on Saturday that a
designated employee accidentally uploaded the
company's unaudited draft financial
results for the quarter ended 31 December
2025 to their personal WhatsApp status. The
insurer clarified that the status uploaded
on 9th January 2026 was deleted within an
hour of the  Error being detected Vedanta The
National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) has
approved the scheme of arrangement between
mining joint Vedanta Limited and its
subsidiary Talwandi Sabo Power Limited
TSPL Lemon Tree Hotels The Lemon Tree
Hotels board approved a composite scheme that will see the
demerger of its subsidiary
FL Hotels, which will house the group's
property assets and is slated for a separate
listing on the BSE and NSE within the
next 12 to 15 months Mahindra and
Mahindra MNM The auto major reported a whopping
27% year-on-year jump in total sales
clocking 8,551
units in December 2025 compared
to 67,252
units in the year-ago period driven by
stellar performance in its utility
vehicle portfolio Indian Renewable
Energy Development Agency IRDA The Navratna
company reported on Friday post market
hours a net profit of  ₹584.9
crore for the quarter ended 31 December
25 climbing 37.5%
YoY and compared to ₹425.4
crore in the corresponding quarter last
year.  Shriram Finance Global credit
rating agency MES Ratings has revised
the outlook on Shriram Finance to positive
from stable while affirming its Ba1
long-term corporate family rating.
Following the company's announcement of a
strategic equity tie-up with M&A Bank.
The Phoenix Mills The company reported a
robust 20% year-on-year growth in total
retail consumption to ₹4,787
crore for the quarter ended December 31, 2025,
while consumption for the first nine months of
FY26 rose 15% to approximately ₹1,122
crore.
ExxonNobel India The company announced a
significant reshuffle of its business on
Friday, appointing Parth Jindal,
Managing Director of JSW Paints
and JSW Siemens, as its new
Chairman and Additional Director in a non-
executive category, effective January 9,
2026. Disclaimer: This article provides
stock market news for international purposes
only and should not be construed as
investment advice.